Well, uh, come on.
There's over 200 questions.
(Leonard:)And look at some of these things.
"Sheldon is to camaraderie
as the space shuttle is to blank."
There are a number of acceptable answers.
For example, C, near-Earth transport.
But certainly not B, avocado rancher.
Your essay: I'd have better luck
making friends...
...if I wait till the Cylons take over?
(Leonard:)Please.
(Leonard:)Hold on. I put some real work into that.
(Penny:)Yes, well,
it's better than what Wolowitz did.
(Sheldon:)He drew a raccoon with what appears
to be a distended scrotum.
It's kind of cute.
- Uh, till you get to the scrotum.
- Yeah.
(Sheldon:)What hope do I have for establishing
new relationships, given that my friends...
...could not take a few hours
out of their lives to help me?
Well, Sheldon, I'm not going
to defend a big-balled raccoon.
Oh, I don't see how you could.
Ugh. What I'm trying to say
is that you can't approach this...